you run your whole business on WordPress
but to manage your to-do an ongoing
project you have to leave your WordPress
dashboard every time it sucks right say
goodbye to platform switching and gain
complete control over your everyday
projects with fln boards a standalone
project management solution with
Limitless possibilities SN boards is the
future of project management either
you're a solopreneur agency owner or
running remote job never lose your focus
on work unlike SAS fluent boards has no
limitations while making projects tasks
or even assigning teammates take
productivity to a New Height with
multi-stage workflow combine board view
manage thousands of tasks assign all
your team members and enjoy a blissful
management experience your job is half
done built by a trustworthy team that's
powering 750k plus businesses fluent
boards can seamlessly integrate with
other fluent products like like fluent
CRM fluent forms and many more coming on
the way easily add your CRM contexts to
any board or task giving your team
immediate access to client information
plus if you need to run any automation
for these contacts you can now easily do
so using fluen crm's pre-built
automation options shaping their project
Journey with
you there's also fluent support
integration available in fluent boards
good news for fluent for forms users too
create form link them with fluent boards
and share them anywhere with your
clients now when they submit the form a
task will be created automatically on
that specific board all in sync talking
about synchronization all the task
collaboration comments notifications are
in the same place no worries of missing
out on any update plus unlock the
hardbeat of project success with fluent
board's super fast email notification
that's not all with fluent boards take
control as The Gatekeepers of all your
data and hosted yourself with a strong
data privacy and smart role management
system not to mention paint your project
boards with colors labels high-risk
background images that can add an extra
charm in the daily life work experience
set and achieve the right goals assign
due dates Advance task filtering and get
meing ful insights all inside fluent
boards which is super convenient and
practical so are you ready to experience
a groundbreaking approach to handling
your next project and turn your project
management headaches into a symphony of
productivity let's step together into
the future of project management with
fluent boards hurry up and grab it cuz
project management was never so fluent